<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Envoys of Dissonance</title>
    <link>https://yoursite.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Envoys of Dissonance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 23:10:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yoursite.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Officers</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/page/officers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 23:10:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/page/officers/</guid>
      <description>Rank Information Our ranks go as such:
 Dragon - The Leader of the Free Company, and highest-ranking officer Soldier - Second-rank members; These members have shown to be incredibly helpful in some way, be it crafting, gathering, or instructing new players. Sorcerer - Third-rank members; A group primarily made of some of the oldest and most trusted members of the Company Envoy - Currently the lowest rank; nothing special about these members, except that they make up the bulk of our Company!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musicbot</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/news/musicbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:48:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/news/musicbot/</guid>
      <description>Hello, Envoys! This is Nexan, the maintainer of our current Music Bot, the Ironworks Orchestrion™. It can be utilized by using the commands found here. Please note, not everyone will have access to all the commands, as most members of the server are only able to use the basic commands. Should we decide that more commands are needed for regular members, we can expand that.
Friendly reminder, if you use the new 🎵 Ironworks Orchestrion 🎵, please remember to disconnect it from the channel after use, as it&amp;rsquo;s not currently set up to auto-disconnect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoilers</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/news/spoilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:47:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/news/spoilers/</guid>
      <description>Please use the leeks-and-onions-endwalker channel at your own risk. It is for content that has been leaked for endwalker only. Information as it&amp;rsquo;s been released should still be posted to endwalker-end </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dispatch</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/news/dispatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:45:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/news/dispatch/</guid>
      <description>This is about Dispatches.
They used to be weekly, now they&amp;rsquo;re whenever we need to tell people about things.
New Cool Posts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:29:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About - General We are the Envoys of Dissonance, a Free Company from Gilgamesh in the Aether Datacenter. We are allied with the Maelstrom, and our tag is &amp;laquo;ENVOY&amp;raquo;. Founded on 7/22/2020, we
Most of us are on almost every evening, and as such we do not have a regular &amp;ldquo;meeting&amp;rdquo; time. Our Company Leader, Billy (A.K.A. Kelvius Argent), has been trying to get a group together for raiding for several months now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://yoursite.example.com/2021/10/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 23:41:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yoursite.example.com/2021/10/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post here
it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be boring, sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
